Zhijiang Rongliang Wuxian Tech (Zhejiang) Co., Ltd. / Zhejiang Yanhe Culture Tech Co., Ltd.
Stop.
What's wrong, Lord Su?
Under the law of the Great Tang,
is playing the qin a crime?
I came here
just to see
this famous qin academy.
I heard this is Master Han's life's work.
Now it seems
it's nothing special.
Shut up!
Say it again.
It's the same even if I say it a hundred times.
Your Shuxiang Qin Academy is trash.
If you have the skills,
then get on the stage
and compete with me in playing the qin.
This is too much.
Send the body to the morgue.
I need to perform an autopsy.
But it hasn't been seven days since Master passed.
Put it here.
Aren't you scared?
What are you doing?
Stop pretending.
Before the old man died,
did he give you "Nanshan Youtai"?
No, he didn't.
You're secretly keeping "Nanshan Youtai".
It's a priceless music score.
You are mistaken, senior brother.
I don't understand music scores at all.
Why would I hide them?
Still acting in front of me, huh?
Where did you hide it?
I really don't know.
Nanshan Youtai
is the essence of our master's lifelong learning.
He kept saying
he would pass the score to one of us,
but he never specified who.
I've always known that
in his heart,
only one disciple is worthy of Nanshan Youtai,
and that's me.
Tell me where it is hidden.
Xiao.
Master was clearly killed by that
Western Regions demon.
And he even came here today
to humiliate us like this.
I am the eldest senior brother.
My zither skills are the best.
If I can get the score,
I can get revenge.
Xiaoxiao.
The old man is dead,
and now I have Nanshan Youtai.
From now on,
I am the number one musician in the world.
Then...
w-what about
the other two senior brothers?
If you dare tell anyone,
I'll tear you to pieces.
There won't be any more reanimations.
No poisoning.
No wounds.
Suddenly bleeding from all orifices and dying.
This is too bizarre.
Could it be
that this zither music really has magic
and can kill?
The Human Bone Wolf Head Zither.
Such a sinister instrument
shouldn't exist in this world.
I've never seen such an evil thing.
Oh no, Cui Yujing went to the arena.
Go.
Okay.
This Western Region demon is doing evil,
pushing people too far!
I, Cui Yujing,
will enforce justice on behalf of Heaven today
and for my master,
take revenge!
Good!
Competing with me in zither
will cost you your life.
Do you dare?
Although I don't know
what tricks you used to make my master die suddenly,
today
you will definitely be defeated by me.
One stick of incense
decides life and death.
Your time of death has come.
It's 'Nan Shan You Tai'.
Ashina Xiao is dead for sure.
I think this side will definitely lose.
Excuse me.
Senior brother is indeed amazing.
Teach that Western Region man a good lesson.
'Nan Shan You Tai'.
What is 'Nan Shan You Tai'?
This 'Nan Shan You Tai' is a masterpiece.
It is said that this sheet music has been lost for a long time.
It's indeed 'Nan Shan You Tai' left by Musician Han.
To hear this piece,
I would die without regrets.
Yes, yes.
Cui Yujing's music has such great momentum.
He's bound to win.
Teach that Western Region man a good lesson.
Not necessarily.
What?
Look at Cui Yujing's face.
Good!
He's lost his mind.
I won.
I won!
I am the best in the world!
Stop quickly!
Someone died.
Is Cui Yujing dead?
This Western Region demon.
Did he kill someone?
Stop.
Stop right there.
Daring to kill in the street.
I will arrest you.
I was just playing the zither.
How is that killing?
Are your Tang Dynasty laws so trifling,
or are you deliberately oppressing me, a foreigner?
You!
Who exactly are you?
I am a soul
that shouldn't exist in this world.
Who else? Who else?
I am waiting for you.
I think it was Ashina Xiao who killed him.
He did it to avenge Chu Feng.
The motive is very clear.
But we can't arrest him
based on the absurd claim
that zither music can kill.
Are you listening to me?
Can you be quiet for a moment?
Don't you think my playing
is a little different from Cui Yujing's?
Can you say something useful?
What's the difference?
It's obvious you don't understand zither music.
The one I have
is the real 'Nanshan Youtai'.
The real 'Nanshan Youtai'?
Where did you get it?
It's from my collection.
I'm a distinguished guest of Prince Ling.
I bought it for 200 taels of gold.
If my guess is right,
Cui Yujing's copy of 'Nanshan Youtai'
is fake.
He mixed
the evil Western Regions melody,
'Chonggu Yao', into it.
'Chonggu Yao'?
Legend has it that 'Chonggu Yao'
can trigger the Gu insects in the body
and kill.
This perfectly aligns with the idea
of zither music killing people.
Stop crying.
Everyone, come and take a look.
This is the famous yellow wine of Fangzhou.
This is the Jiuyin Gu from the Western Regions.
Put the eggs
into tea or wine,
and let someone consume them.
It takes two to three months at the fastest,
or two to three years at the slowest.
When the Gu matures,
it devours the internal organs.
This is the Jiuyin Gu.
Because of the unique brewing process of yellow wine,
it has a strong reaction to the Gu.
Driven by the evil melody 'Chonggu Yao',
this bug will backfire on its host,
causing them
to bleed from the seven orifices and die.
It must be that person from the Western Regions.
Lord Su, please arrest him quickly.
The murderer
might not be Ashina Xiao.
Because this melody
was played by the victim himself.
The evil melody of 'Chonggu Yao' was mixed
into his sheet music for 'Nanshan Youtai'.
Musician Han
and Cui Yujing
both died because of this.
I also checked the entry and exit records of Fangzhou for the past three months.
Ashina Xiao only arrived five days ago.
He had no time to poison them at all.
Then who is the murderer?
The poisoner
might not be Ashina Xiao.
But Master and Senior Brother
both died competing with him in playing the zither.
He is definitely involved.
Therefore,
Ashina Xiao must have an accomplice behind him.
This person
must not only have the ability
but also the time to enter and exit the Zither Academy freely
to complete the poisoning.
This means that
everyone present here
is a suspect.